<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Tokens version="1.0">
	<File path="Protocols/TTMessageControllerDelegate.html">
		
		<Token>
			<TokenIdentifier>//apple_ref/occ/intf/TTMessageControllerDelegate</TokenIdentifier>
			<Abstract type="html">A protocol for the object that implements the backend logic for the
TTMessageController. This object is responsible for delivering the message
that was composed in the view controller when the user chooses the send option.
It receive a message when the user cancels the creation of a message or when
they press the plus icon in a recipient field.</Abstract>
			<DeclaredIn>TTMessageControllerDelegate.h</DeclaredIn>
			
			<NodeRef refid="286"/>
		</Token>
		
		
		<Token>
			<TokenIdentifier>//apple_ref/occ/intfm/TTMessageControllerDelegate/composeController:didSendFields:</TokenIdentifier>
			<Abstract type="html">Received when the user touches the send button, indicating they wish to send
their message. Implementations should send the message represented by the
supplied fields. The fields array contains subclasses of TTMessageField. Its
last object is the body of the message, contained within a TTMessageTextField.</Abstract>
			<DeclaredIn>TTMessageControllerDelegate.h</DeclaredIn>			
			
			<Declaration>- (void)composeController:(TTMessageController *)controller didSendFields:(NSArray *)fields</Declaration>
			
			
			<Anchor>//api/name/composeController:didSendFields:</Anchor>
		</Token>
		
		<Token>
			<TokenIdentifier>//apple_ref/occ/intfm/TTMessageControllerDelegate/composeControllerWillCancel:</TokenIdentifier>
			<Abstract type="html">Received when the user has chosen to cancel creating their message. Upon
returning, the TTMessageController will be dismissed. Implementations
can use this callback to cleanup any resources.</Abstract>
			<DeclaredIn>TTMessageControllerDelegate.h</DeclaredIn>			
			
			<Declaration>- (void)composeControllerWillCancel:(TTMessageController *)controller</Declaration>
			
			
			<Anchor>//api/name/composeControllerWillCancel:</Anchor>
		</Token>
		
		<Token>
			<TokenIdentifier>//apple_ref/occ/intfm/TTMessageControllerDelegate/composeControllerShowRecipientPicker:</TokenIdentifier>
			<Abstract type="html">Received in response to the user touching a contact add button. This method
should prepare and present a view for the user to choose a contact. Upon
choosing a contact, that contact should be added to the field.</Abstract>
			<DeclaredIn>TTMessageControllerDelegate.h</DeclaredIn>			
			
			<Declaration>- (void)composeControllerShowRecipientPicker:(TTMessageController *)controller</Declaration>
			
			
			<Anchor>//api/name/composeControllerShowRecipientPicker:</Anchor>
		</Token>
		
	</File>
</Tokens>